<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on 23Ro&#39;s Digest</title>
    <link>http://www.23ro.de/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on 23Ro&#39;s Digest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:44:51 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.23ro.de/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the humble mindspace of 23Ro</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:44:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/</guid>
      <description>A primer This is dedicated to all the time spent in front of my computers. Exploring new projects, oportunities and studying. In all it&amp;rsquo;s glory, I present you, the humble inventions, findings, and collections of myself, friends, family and fools. This website is built with hugo, where content is mainly written in markdown and insanely fast converted to a static website - it&amp;rsquo;s fun.
I tend to write about all sorts of technology, sometimes about the business world around development, software engineering, my hobbies and little projects that I pursue to keep life interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mamiya Rb 67 Professional S - a beast of a camera</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/mamiya-rb-67/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 15:59:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/mamiya-rb-67/</guid>
      <description>April, 2019. 49 years after its premiere on the photography market, I decided to purchase a Mamiya RB 67. Whilst I already had experience with medium format TLRs (the WZFO Start-B), which we had acquired for a vintage wedding of one of my closest friends, and which sparked my interested in analogue photography, it turned out that the Mamiya RB 67 is a completely different beast. Capable of pictures rivalling modern digital cameras in look and detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A life without advertisements - Pihole DNS Adblocker</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/pihole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 18:04:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/pihole/</guid>
      <description>You have enough of advertisement? Yes, who hasn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip; You say you are using an AdBlocker? What if I tell you, there is a much better option than using an AdBlocker. It will safe internet traffic, it will boost loading speeds, and it will give you much more control about everything. Sounds tempting right?
So, if you have a spare one of these: , or even if you don&amp;rsquo;t, check out this tutorial!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WZFO Start-B - a medium format camera</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/wzfo-start-b-twin-lens-reflex-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 22:23:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/wzfo-start-b-twin-lens-reflex-camera/</guid>
      <description>Recently one of my best friends married, and I took the honor of being his best man. The wedding took place in a historical franconian castle. The pairs wish was that all the guests follow the theme &amp;ldquo;vintage&amp;rdquo;. This being a very broad theme, I decided to follow the rules and buy some ol fashioned clothes/a old fashioned suite, to be as appropriately dressed as possible. During my research I stumbled over some old footage, and eventually decided to actually purchase a old film camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Berlin Kreuzberg Trash Part One</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/berlin-kreuzberg-trash-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 22:40:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/berlin-kreuzberg-trash-part-one/</guid>
      <description>My daily commute to work includes walking a beautiful strip of berlin roads. Namely: Prinzenstraße, and its side-, and crossroads. I pass a lot of green until I reach our office (from Moritzplatz to Gitschinerstraße), conveniently located next to a brothel and close to Prinzenstraße U-Bahn Station, in one of the rear courtyard of a Gitschiner Straße building (luckily freshly renovated). However, this beautiful path is frequently destroyed by what I encounter there&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:07:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/about/</guid>
      <description>My Name is Maximilian, most of my time is spent on my favourite topic - technology. I work as a product owner, developer, manager, mostly on the Fintech SaaS industry.
Besides the passion for technology, I like taking photos of everyday things - check out my photography page:
23ro.photography and find me on 
and spend time on my two wheeled toys: a Cagiva Raptor 650 IE (2006) &amp;amp; a Cagive Mito Evo (2001).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>legal disclaimer</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/legal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:07:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/legal/</guid>
      <description>This blog is built, maintained, hosted, and completely located in Germany. In order to comply with the §5 TMG (Telemediengesetz) I have hereby added a legally correct disclaimer. As the content on this page might be related to my business activites, I am bound to add this section even though you will only see my private notes here. There will be no advertisement on this page, or monetization efforts. So this is solely a safety measure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>