<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on 23Ro&#39;s Digest</title>
    <link>http://www.23ro.de/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on 23Ro&#39;s Digest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:11:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.23ro.de/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1000 Days - A quick retrospective on switching to straight edge</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/1000days/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:11:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/1000days/</guid>
      <description>1000 Days My blog has been pretty dead lately. Although I have the goal of writing one blog entry a month, I keep on pushing this task due to various reasons. And even with COVID, my life got busier than ever before.
During these intense, but fun, days I got reminded by an app on my phone about one big thing, this being:
Exactly one thousand days ago I decided to not consume any alcohol, nicotine, or (for the sake of completeness) any other drug anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mamiya Rb 67 Professional S - a beast of a camera</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/mamiya-rb-67/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 15:59:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/mamiya-rb-67/</guid>
      <description>April, 2019. 49 years after its premiere on the photography market, I decided to purchase a Mamiya RB 67. Whilst I already had experience with medium format TLRs (the WZFO Start-B), which we had acquired for a vintage wedding of one of my closest friends, and which sparked my interested in analogue photography, it turned out that the Mamiya RB 67 is a completely different beast. Capable of pictures rivalling modern digital cameras in look and detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A life without advertisements - Pihole DNS Adblocker</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/pihole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 18:04:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/pihole/</guid>
      <description>You have enough of advertisement? Yes, who hasn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip; You say you are using an AdBlocker? What if I tell you, there is a much better option than using an AdBlocker. It will safe internet traffic, it will boost loading speeds, and it will give you much more control about everything. Sounds tempting right?
So, if you have a spare one of these: , or even if you don&amp;rsquo;t, check out this tutorial!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WZFO Start-B - a medium format camera</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/wzfo-start-b-twin-lens-reflex-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 22:23:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/wzfo-start-b-twin-lens-reflex-camera/</guid>
      <description>Recently one of my best friends married, and I took the honor of being his best man. The wedding took place in a historical franconian castle. The pairs wish was that all the guests follow the theme &amp;ldquo;vintage&amp;rdquo;. This being a very broad theme, I decided to follow the rules and buy some ol fashioned clothes/a old fashioned suite, to be as appropriately dressed as possible. During my research I stumbled over some old footage, and eventually decided to actually purchase a old film camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Berlin Kreuzberg Trash Part One</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/berlin-kreuzberg-trash-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 22:40:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/berlin-kreuzberg-trash-part-one/</guid>
      <description>My daily commute to work includes walking a beautiful strip of berlin roads. Namely: Prinzenstraße, and its side-, and crossroads. I pass a lot of green until I reach our office (from Moritzplatz to Gitschinerstraße), conveniently located next to a brothel and close to Prinzenstraße U-Bahn Station, in one of the rear courtyard of a Gitschiner Straße building (luckily freshly renovated). However, this beautiful path is frequently destroyed by what I encounter there&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVED initial landing page - more a first post</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/initial-landing-page-but-more-a-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 22:50:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/initial-landing-page-but-more-a-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Information: This went live initially on 2018-04-09 at 00:44:51+02:00 I decided to move this very nice first landing page to the posts sections, as it rather appears to me as a real post.
A primer This is dedicated to all the time spent in front of computers. Finding a true way to express oneself in projects, and beginning to make a small private blog a habit. In all it&amp;rsquo;s glory, I will present you, the humble inventions, findings, and collections of myself, friends, family and fools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>