<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to the humble mindspace of 23Ro on 23Ro&#39;s Digest</title>
    <link>http://www.23ro.de/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to the humble mindspace of 23Ro on 23Ro&#39;s Digest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:44:51 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.23ro.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Berlin Kreuzberg Trash Part One</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/berlin-kreuzberg-trash-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 22:40:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/berlin-kreuzberg-trash-part-one/</guid>
      <description>My daily commute to work includes walking a beautiful strip of berlin roads. Namely: Prinzenstraße, and its side-, and crossroads. I pass a lot of green until I reach our office (from Moritzplatz to Gitschinerstraße), conveniently located next to a brothel and close to Prinzenstraße U-Bahn Station, in one of the rear courtyard of a Gitschiner Straße building (luckily freshly renovated). However, this beautiful path is frequently destroyed by what I encounter there&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Is Golangday #1</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/sunday-is-golangday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 18:22:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/sunday-is-golangday/</guid>
      <description>Sunday is Golangday will be a new series of golang related learnings of mine. As I have just started learning Golang, this will be mainly focusing on the basics of the go programming language.
 Gopher image by Renee French, licensed under Creative Commons 3.0 Attributions license.  What is golang Go (by Google) is a programming language created at Google in 2009. Not to be confused with Go! (a functional programming language developed by Francis McCabe, and Keith Clark and first appeared in 2003).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access tokens, passwords, sensitive data, and how to avoid a data breach</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/acces-tokens-passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 22:49:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/acces-tokens-passwords/</guid>
      <description>Some words about privacy (and data privacy) and how to assure it Many people consider the terms data protection, data privacy, and privacy in general to be synonyms, and even though they are all closely related, they complement each other without ever being the same.
privacy: the quality or state of being apart from company or observation1
data privacy: &amp;hellip;is about authorized access — who has it and who defines it2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVED initial landing page - more a first post</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/initial-landing-page-but-more-a-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 22:50:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/initial-landing-page-but-more-a-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Information: This went live initially on 2018-04-09 at 00:44:51+02:00 I decided to move this very nice first landing page to the posts sections, as it rather appears to me as a real post.
A primer This is dedicated to all the time spent in front of computers. Finding a true way to express oneself in projects, and beginning to make a small private blog a habit. In all it&amp;rsquo;s glory, I will present you, the humble inventions, findings, and collections of myself, friends, family and fools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How-To: Increment Selected Values Inside Insert Statement</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/how-to-increment-selected-values-inside-insert-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 01:16:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/how-to-increment-selected-values-inside-insert-statement/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my first snippet addition to this website. I hope you find this as helpful as I find it sometimes.
Why would I need this? Imagine you want to fill a field of a table with a sequenctially value, but do not have any ID for a sequence and are using PostgreSQL, and you also already have information in this table that you want to append on. Well there is this option to use the internal ID (CID) provided by PostgreSQL, but this only works to a certain extent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Second Day With Hugo</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/a-second-day-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:43:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/a-second-day-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Second entry - first commit After setting things up initially in a Mac environment and creating a new post, why not doing the same for windows? &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; Bad idead
Still, I&amp;rsquo;m getting it and slowly things are coming together Setting Hugo up on a windows machine is not utterly complex, but also not as fluent of an experience as on linux, or mac. One might wonder why I have to deal with three different environments at all?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Day With Hugo</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/a-new-day-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 23:23:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/a-new-day-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Initial Entry - no commit Just doing the setup like described in the quickstart.
I&amp;rsquo;m trying to figure out what I&amp;rsquo;m doing here So setting up hugo was a smooth experience on my macbook.
1st Step:
Installing the depencie via brew install hugo
2nd Step:
Installing the desired them as a submodule via git add submodule &amp;lt;ADD_URI_TO_DESIRED_THEME_GIT&amp;gt; &amp;lt;PATH_IF_NECESSARY&amp;gt;;
3rd Step:
Adding a first post via hugo new posts/a-new-day-with-hugo.md
Et voilà and here we are.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>