<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>things on 23Ro&#39;s Digest</title>
    <link>http://www.23ro.de/tags/things/</link>
    <description>Recent content in things on 23Ro&#39;s Digest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:11:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.23ro.de/tags/things/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1000 Days - A quick retrospective on switching to straight edge</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/1000days/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:11:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/1000days/</guid>
      <description>1000 Days My blog has been pretty dead lately. Although I have the goal of writing one blog entry a month, I keep on pushing this task due to various reasons. And even with COVID, my life got busier than ever before.
During these intense, but fun, days I got reminded by an app on my phone about one big thing, this being:
Exactly one thousand days ago I decided to not consume any alcohol, nicotine, or (for the sake of completeness) any other drug anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Decade ~ 2020</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/happy-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/happy-2020/</guid>
      <description>Happy new year and a good start into the 21st century twenties A healthy and awesome start into the new year to everyone!
As the new decade begins, many people tend to set themselves additional new years resolutions. I thoroughly don&amp;rsquo;t believe in this particular tradition.
But I believe in kicking bad habits - independently from any specific day of a year. So I did. And encourage everyone to do the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A life without advertisements - Pihole DNS Adblocker</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/pihole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 18:04:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/pihole/</guid>
      <description>You have enough of advertisement? Yes, who hasn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip; You say you are using an AdBlocker? What if I tell you, there is a much better option than using an AdBlocker. It will safe internet traffic, it will boost loading speeds, and it will give you much more control about everything. Sounds tempting right?
So, if you have a spare one of these: , or even if you don&amp;rsquo;t, check out this tutorial!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVED initial landing page - more a first post</title>
      <link>http://www.23ro.de/posts/initial-landing-page-but-more-a-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 22:50:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.23ro.de/posts/initial-landing-page-but-more-a-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Information: This went live initially on 2018-04-09 at 00:44:51+02:00 I decided to move this very nice first landing page to the posts sections, as it rather appears to me as a real post.
A primer This is dedicated to all the time spent in front of computers. Finding a true way to express oneself in projects, and beginning to make a small private blog a habit. In all it&amp;rsquo;s glory, I will present you, the humble inventions, findings, and collections of myself, friends, family and fools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>